<process draft="false" dev-studio-version="7.6.01.02">
  <process-def name=":AO-AD-IBM_Tivoli_Storage_Manager:v5.5:Schedule:Update Schedule">
    <parameters>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>adapter name [Optional]
The name of the adapter that is enabled on the Peer.
The default adapter name is IBMTSMActor</description>
        <from>adapter name</from>
        <to>adapter name</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="true">
        <description>UPDATE SCHEDULE:

This wrapper updates a predefined client schedule.

Sample Item Xml: 

&lt;items&gt;
	&lt;item&gt;
		&lt;operation-name&gt;update-schedule&lt;/operation-name&gt;
		&lt;timeout-secs&gt;30&lt;/timeout-secs&gt;
		&lt;command-options&gt;
			&lt;domain-name&gt;standard&lt;/domain-name&gt;
			&lt;schedule-name&gt;schedule00002-xyz-1&lt;/schedule-name&gt;
			&lt;type&gt;client&lt;/type&gt;
			&lt;description&gt;this my desctiption-new updated description&lt;/description&gt;
			&lt;action&gt;incremental&lt;/action&gt;
			&lt;options&gt;
				&lt;subdir&gt;yes&lt;/subdir&gt;
			&lt;/options&gt;
			&lt;!-- here we are updating "description" and "objects" --&gt;
			&lt;objects&gt;C:\ab.txt&lt;/objects&gt;
			&lt;priority&gt;5&lt;/priority&gt;
			&lt;start-date&gt;10/02/2009&lt;/start-date&gt;
			&lt;start-time&gt;10:00&lt;/start-time&gt;
			&lt;duration&gt;2&lt;/duration&gt;
			&lt;duration-unit&gt;hours&lt;/duration-unit&gt;
			&lt;period&gt;1&lt;/period&gt;
			&lt;period-unit&gt;days&lt;/period-unit&gt;
			&lt;day-of-week&gt;sunday&lt;/day-of-week&gt;
			&lt;expiration&gt;never&lt;/expiration&gt;
		&lt;/command-options&gt;
	&lt;/item&gt;
&lt;/items&gt;


Elements' Description: 

operation-name [Required]: the operation name.
Valid values: update-schedule.

timeout-secs [optional]: the time out second. the unit of this parameter is "second". 
Valid value: any integer greater than 0;
Default value: 60.

command-options [Required]: within this element we provide the informations (elements) such as &lt;domain-name&gt;, &lt;schedule-name&gt;, &lt;options&gt; etc.

domain-name [Required]: Specifies the name of the policy domain to which this schedule belongs. 
Valid values: The domain name of targeted schedule.

schedule-name [Required]: Specifies the name of the schedule to be created. You can specify up to 30 characters for the name. 

Valid values: The schedule name of targeted schedule.

type [optional]: Specifies that a schedule for a client is being created. 
Valid values: client. 
Default value: client.

description [optional]: Specifies a description of the schedule. You can specify up to 255 characters for the description. 
Valid values: Any string. 
Default value: Ignored.

action [Optional]: Specifies the action that occurs when this schedule is processed

Valid Values: Incremental, Selective, Archive, Restore, Retrieve, Imagebackup, Imagerestore, Command, Macro.

Incremental 
Specifies that the schedule backs up all files that are new or that have changed since the last incremental backup. Incremental also backs up any file for which all existing backups may have expired. 
Selective 
Specifies that the schedule backs up only files that are specified with the objects parameter. 
Archive 
Specifies that the schedule archives files that are specified with the objects parameter. 
Restore
Specifies that the schedule restores files that are specified with the objects parameter. 
Retrieve 
Specifies that the schedule retrieves files that are specified with the objects parameter. 
Imagebackup
Specifies that the schedule backs up logical volumes that are specified with the objects parameter. 
Imagestore 
Specifies that the schedule restores logical volumes that are specified with the objects parameter. 
Command 
Specifies that the schedule processes a client operating system command or script that is specified with the objects parameter. 
Macro 
Specifies that a client processes a macro whose file name is specified with the objects parameter. 

Default value: Ignored.


options [Optional]: The options (if any) given to perform the action defined in the schedule.

Example: 
&lt;options&gt;
	&lt;subdir&gt;yes&lt;/subdir&gt;
	&lt;domain&gt;all –local –c: systemobjects&lt;/domain&gt;
&lt;/options&gt;

Here, we are giving two options namely “subdir” and “domain”. For detail about options refer the options’ documents of other operations whom this adapter support.
Valid values: options that different type of operations support.
Default value: Ignored.

objects [optional]: Specifies the objects for which the specified action is performed. Use a single space between each object. This parameter is required (needed) except when action=incremental (notice, in incremental case, all files that are new or that have changed since the last incremental get backed up.) If the action is a backup, archive, retrieve, or restore operation, the objects are file spaces, directories, or logical volumes. If the action is to run a command or macro, the object is the name of the command or macro to run.
 
Valid values: file, directories, logical volumes (with absolute path), commands, macros etc. 
Default value: Ignored.

priority [Optional]: Specifies the priority value for the schedule. 

Valid values: any integer from 1 to 10, with 1 being the highest priority and 10 being the lowest.
Default value: Ignored. 

start-date [Optional]: Specifies the date for the beginning of the window in which the schedule is first processed. 

Valid values: 

* MM/DD/YYYY (example- 09/15/1998.)

* TODAY (tag to current date.)

* ‘TODAY + days’ (days = some natural number, 0 &lt;= days &lt;= 9999; tag to show the date which is after “days” number of days from current date. Example- ‘TODAY+3’.)

* ‘+days’ (days = some natural number, 0 &lt;= days &lt;= 9999; tag to show the date which is after “days” number of days from current date. Example- ‘+3’.)

Default value: Ignored.


start-time [Optional]: Specifies the time for the beginning of the window in which the schedule is first processed. 

Valid values: 

* HH:MM:SS (example- 01:01:2001).

* NOW (tag to current time.)

* NOW + HH:MM (tag to show the time after ‘HH’ hours &amp; ‘MM’ minutes the current time.)

* ‘+HH:MM’ (same as above.)

* NOW – HH:MM (tag to show the time before ‘HH’ hours &amp; ‘MM’ minutes the current time.) 

* ‘-HH:MM’ (same as above.)

Default value: Ignored.

duration [Optional]: This is time-length after start of any startup window, within which the action must take place. If duration-unit is set to be ‘indefinite’ then this parameter is ignored and action would take place at any instant during active startup window.

Valid values: Any integer from 1 to 999.
Default value: Ignored.

duration-unit [Optional] : unit of duration.

Valid values: Minutes, Hours, Days, Indefinite.

Minutes 
Specifies that the duration of the window is defined in minutes. 
Hours 
Specifies that the duration of the window is defined in hours. 
Days 
Specifies that the duration of the window is defined in days. 
Indefinite 
Specifies that the startup window of the scheduled operation has an indefinite duration. The schedule can run any time after the scheduled start time, until the schedule expires. You cannot specify duration-unit = indefinite, unless you specify period-unit = Onetime. 

Default Value: Ignored.

period [Optional] : Specifies the length of time between startup windows for this schedule. This value is ignored if we set period-unit to be ‘Onetime’.

Valid values: Any integer from 1 to 999. 
Default value: Ignored.


period-unit [optional]: unit of period. 

Valid values: Hours, Days, Weeks, Months, Years, Onetime.

Hours 
Specifies that the time between startup windows is in hours. 
Days 
Specifies that the time between startup windows is in days. 
Weeks 
Specifies that the time between startup windows is in weeks. 
Months 
Specifies that the time between startup windows is in months. 
Note:
When you specify period-units = ‘Months’, the scheduled operation will be processed each month on the same date. For example, If the start date for the scheduled operation is 02/04/1998, the schedule will process on the 4th of every month thereafter. However, if the date is not valid for the next month, then the scheduled operation will be processed on the last valid date in the month. Thereafter, subsequent operations are based on this new date. For example, if the start date is 03/31/1998, the next month's operation will be scheduled for 04/30/1998. Thereafter, all subsequent operations will be on the 30th of the month until February. Because February has only 28 days, the operation will be scheduled for 02/28/1999. Subsequent operations will be processed on the 28th of the month. 
Years 
Specifies that the time between startup windows for the schedule is in years. 
Note:
When you specify period-unit = ‘Years’, the scheduled operation will be processed on the same month and date of each year. For example, if the start date for the scheduled operation is 02/29/2004, the next year's scheduled operation will be 02/28/2005 because February only has 28 days. Thereafter, subsequent operations will be scheduled for February 28th. 
Onetime 
Specifies that the schedule processes once. 


Default value: Ignored.


day-of-week [optional]: Specifies the day of the week on which the startup window for the schedule begins. This parameter is optional. If the start date and start time fall on a day that does not correspond to a day you specify, the start date and start time will be shifted forward in 24-hour increments until the day-of-week parameter is satisfied. 
If you select a value for day-of-week other than ‘Any’, and depending on the values for period and period-unit, schedules may not be processed when you would expect. 
Valid values: Any, Weekday, Weekend, Sunday, Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday.

Any 
Specifies that the startup window can begin on any day of the week. 
Weekday 
Specifies that the startup window can begin on Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, or Friday. 
Weekend 
Specifies that the startup window can begin on Saturday or Sunday. 
Sunday
Specifies that the startup window begins on Sunday. 
Monday 
Specifies that the startup window begins on Monday. 
Tuesday 
Specifies that the startup window begins on Tuesday. 
Wednesday 
Specifies that the startup window begins on Wednesday. 
Thursday 
Specifies that the startup window begins on Thursday. 
Friday 
Specifies that the startup window begins on Friday. 
Saturday 
Specifies that the startup window begins on Saturday. 

Default value: Ignored.

expiration [Optional]: Specifies the date after which this schedule is no longer used. 

Valid values: Never, MM/DD/YYYY

Never 
Specifies that the schedule never expires. 


MM/DD/YYY
Some date after which the schedule is not longer used (e.g., 01/01/01). If you specify an expiration date, the schedule expires at 23:59:59 on the date you specify. 

Default value: Ignored.
</description>
        <from>items</from>
        <to>items</to>
      </input>
      <output global="false" required="false">
        <to>adapter response</to>
        <from>adapter response</from>
      </output>
    </parameters>
    <access />
    <sequence>
      <call-process>
        <process-name>:AO-AD-IBM_Tivoli_Storage_Manager:Utilities:Execute Request</process-name>
        <parameters>
          <input>
            <from>adapter name</from>
            <to>adapter name</to>
          </input>
          <input>
            <from>items</from>
            <to>items</to>
          </input>
          <input>
            <value>update-schedule</value>
            <to>valid operation name</to>
          </input>
          <output>
            <from>adapter response</from>
            <to>adapter response</to>
          </output>
        </parameters>
        <meta>
          <documentation />
          <run-mode-handling>
            <run-mode>OCP</run-mode>
            <allow-step-into>false</allow-step-into>
          </run-mode-handling>
          <checkpoint>false</checkpoint>
        </meta>
        <after-execution>
          <console-output>
            <type>INFO</type>
            <summary>
              <concat>
                <input>
                  <value></value>
                </input>
              </concat>
            </summary>
            <detail>
              <concat>
                <input>
                  <value></value>
                </input>
              </concat>
            </detail>
          </console-output>
        </after-execution>
        <location>:call-process[1]</location>
      </call-process>
    </sequence>
    <meta>
      <expose-to>
        <consumer>RULE</consumer>
        <consumer>SCHEDULE</consumer>
      </expose-to>
      <documentation>
        <description>
This wrapper updates a predefined client schedule.</description>
        <version></version>
      </documentation>
      <peer-location>
        <location>any</location>
      </peer-location>
      <record-metrics>false</record-metrics>
      <process-id>7d4ab422-cc98-324a-a413-93a1155be066</process-id>
      <author />
      <category />
      <status />
      <keywords />
      <systems />
      <last-modified-by />
      <last-modified>1290597045475</last-modified>
    </meta>
  </process-def>
</process>