<process draft="false" dev-studio-version="20.02.00">
  <process-def name=":AO-AD-Amazon_EC2_REST:Adapter_Actions:v1.0:Instance_Operations:Describe Instances">
    <parameters>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>adapter name    [Optional]
            The name of the adapter use to handle the request.

Default value: AmazonEC2RESTActorAdapter</description>
        <from>adapter name</from>
        <to>adapter name</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>access key    [Optional]
	The AWS access key.</description>
        <from>access key</from>
        <to>access key</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>secret key    [Optional]
	The AWS secret access key.</description>
        <from>secret key</from>
        <to>secret key</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>session token [Optional] : The AWS session token which is generally created for temporary access to users for role based authorization.

Please Note: The temporary access key , secret key and session token to be generated by the user to provide in adapter request.

Please refer below AWS docs for more details

https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_credentials_temp_request.html  

https://docs.aws.amazon.com/cli/latest/reference/sts/assume-role.html
</description>
        <from>session token</from>
        <to>session token</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>region    [Optional]
		The region to communicate with.</description>
        <from>region</from>
        <to>region</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>
instances set [Optional]

One or more instance IDs, in XML structure as below:


&lt;instances-set&gt;
    &lt;!--Zero or more repetitions:--&gt;
    &lt;item&gt;
        &lt;instance-id&gt;&lt;/instance-id&gt;
    &lt;/item&gt;
&lt;/instances-set&gt;
</description>
        <from>instances set</from>
        <to>instances set</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>filter set [Optional]

Filter to retrieve instances based on the specified criteria.

&lt;filter-set&gt;
    &lt;!--Zero or more repetition--&gt;
    &lt;item&gt;
        &lt;name&gt;&lt;/name&gt;
        &lt;value-set&gt;
            &lt;!--Zero or more repetition--&gt;
            &lt;item&gt;
                &lt;value&gt;&lt;/value&gt;
            &lt;/item&gt;
        &lt;/value-set&gt;
    &lt;/item&gt;
&lt;/filter-set&gt;

The following are the available filters.

architecture (Type: String)
	The instance architecture (i386 | x86_64).

availability-zone (Type: String)
	The Availability Zone of the instance.

block-device-mapping.attach-time (Type: Timestamp)
	The attach time for an Amazon EBS volume mapped to the instance, for example, 2010-09-15T17:15:20.000Z.

block-device-mapping.delete-on-termination (Type: Boolean)
	A Boolean that indicates whether the Amazon EBS volume is deleted on instance termination.

block-device-mapping.device-name (Type: String)	
	The device name for the Amazon EBS volume (for example, /dev/sdh or xvdh).

block-device-mapping.status (Type: String)
	The status for the Amazon EBS volume (attaching | attached | detaching | detached).

block-device-mapping.volume-id (Type: String)
	The volume ID of the Amazon EBS volume.

client-token
	The idempotency token you provided when you launched the instance.

dns-name (Type: String)
	The public DNS name of the instance.

group-id (Type: String)
	The ID of the security group for the instance. EC2-Classic only.

group-name (Type: String)
	The name of the security group for the instance. EC2-Classic only.

hypervisor (Type: String)
	The hypervisor type of the instance (ovm | xen).

iam-instance-profile.arn
	The instance profile associated with the instance. Specified as an ARN.

image-id (Type: String)
	The ID of the image used to launch the instance.

instance-id (Type: String)
	The ID of the instance.

instance-lifecycle
	Indicates whether this is a Spot Instance (spot).

instance-state-code
	The state of the instance, as a 16-bit unsigned integer. The high byte is an opaque internal value and should be ignored. The low byte is set based on the state represented. The valid values are: 0 (pending), 16 (running), 32 (shutting-down), 48 (terminated), 64 (stopping), and 80 (stopped).

instance-state-name
	The state of the instance (pending | running | shutting-down | terminated | stopping | stopped).

instance-type
	The type of instance (for example, t2.micro).

instance.group-id
	The ID of the security group for the instance.

instance.group-name 
	The name of the security group for the instance.

ip-address 
	The public IP address of the instance.

kernel-id 
	The kernel ID.

key-name 
	The name of the key pair used when the instance was launched.

launch-index 
	When launching multiple instances, this is the index for the instance in the launch group (for example, 0, 1, 2, and so on).

launch-time 
	The time when the instance was launched.

monitoring-state 	
	Indicates whether monitoring is enabled for the instance (disabled | enabled).

owner-id 
	The AWS account ID of the instance owner.

placement-group-name 
	The name of the placement group for the instance.

platform 
	The platform. Use windows if you have Windows instances; otherwise, leave blank.

private-dns-name 
	The private DNS name of the instance.

private-ip-address 
	The private IP address of the instance.

product-code 
	The product code associated with the AMI used to launch the instance.

product-code.type 
	The type of product code (devpay | marketplace).

ramdisk-id 
	The RAM disk ID.

reason 
	The reason for the current state of the instance (for example, shows "User Initiated [date]" when you stop or terminate the instance). Similar to the state-reason-code filter.

requester-id 
	The ID of the entity that launched the instance on your behalf (for example, AWS Management Console, Auto Scaling, and so on).

reservation-id 
	The ID of the instance's reservation. A reservation ID is created any time you launch an instance. A reservation ID has a one-to-one relationship with an instance launch request, but can be associated with more than one instance if you launch multiple instances using the same launch request. For example, if you launch one instance, you'll get one reservation ID. If you launch ten instances using the same launch request, you'll also get one reservation ID.

root-device-name 
	The name of the root device for the instance (for example, /dev/sda1 or /dev/xvda).

root-device-type 
	The type of root device that the instance uses (ebs | instance-store).

source-dest-check 
	Indicates whether the instance performs source/destination checking. A value of true means that checking is enabled, and false means checking is disabled. The value must be false for the instance to perform network address translation (NAT) in your VPC.

spot-instance-request-id 
	The ID of the Spot Instance request.

state-reason-code 
	The reason code for the state change.

state-reason-message 
	A message that describes the state change.

subnet-id 
	The ID of the subnet for the instance.

tag:key=value 
	The key/value combination of a tag assigned to the resource, where tag:key is the tag's key.

tag-key 
	The key of a tag assigned to the resource. This filter is independent of the tag-value filter. For example, if you use both the filter "tag-key=Purpose" and the filter "tag-value=X", you get any resources assigned both the tag key Purpose (regardless of what the tag's value is), and the tag value X (regardless of what the tag's key is). If you want to list only resources where Purpose is X, see the tag:key=value filter.

tag-value 
	The value of a tag assigned to the resource. This filter is independent of the tag-key filter.

tenancy 
	The tenancy of an instance (dedicated | default).

virtualization-type 
	The virtualization type of the instance (paravirtual | hvm).

vpc-id 
	The ID of the VPC that the instance is running in.

network-interface.description 
	The description of the network interface.

network-interface.subnet-id 
	The ID of the subnet for the network interface.

network-interface.vpc-id 
	The ID of the VPC for the network interface.

network-interface.network-interface.id
	The ID of the network interface.

network-interface.owner-id 
	The ID of the owner of the network interface.

network-interface.availability-zone 
	The Availability Zone for the network interface.

network-interface.requester-id
	The requester ID for the network interface.

network-interface.requester-managed 
	Indicates whether the network interface is being managed by AWS.

network-interface.status 
	The status of the network interface (available) | in-use).

network-interface.mac-address 
	The MAC address of the network interface.

network-interface-private-dns-name
	The private DNS name of the network interface.

network-interface.source-dest-check 
	Whether the network interface performs source/destination checking. A value of true means checking is enabled, and false means checking is disabled. The value must be false for the network interface to perform network address translation (NAT) in your VPC.

network-interface.group-id 
	The ID of a security group associated with the network interface.

network-interface.group-name 
	The name of a security group associated with the network interface.

network-interface.attachment.attachment-id 
	The ID of the interface attachment.

network-interface.attachment.instance-id 
	The ID of the instance to which the network interface is attached.

network-interface.attachment.instance-owner-id 
	The owner ID of the instance to which the network interface is attached.

network-interface.addresses.private-ip-address 
	The private IP address associated with the network interface.

network-interface.attachment.device-index 
	The device index to which the network interface is attached.

network-interface.attachment.status 
	The status of the attachment (attaching | attached | detaching | detached).

network-interface.attachment.attach-time 
	The time that the network interface was attached to an instance.

network-interface.attachment.delete-on-termination 
	Specifies whether the attachment is deleted when an instance is terminated.

network-interface.addresses.primary 
	Specifies whether the IP address of the network interface is the primary private IP address.

network-interface.addresses.association.public-ip 
	The ID of the association of an Elastic IP address with a network interface.

network-interface.addresses.association.ip-owner-id 
	The owner ID of the private IP address associated with the network interface.

association.public-ip 
	The address of the Elastic IP address bound to the network interface.

association.ip-owner-id 
	The owner of the Elastic IP address associated with the network interface.

association.allocation-id 
	The allocation ID returned when you allocated the Elastic IP address for your network interface.

association.association-id 
	The association ID returned when the network interface was associated with an IP address.</description>
        <from>filter set</from>
        <to>filter set</to>
      </input>
      <output global="false" required="false">
        <description>The adapter response containing the results. </description>
        <to>adapter response</to>
        <from>adapter response</from>
      </output>
    </parameters>
    <access />
    <sequence>
      <call-process>
        <process-name>:AO-AD-Amazon_EC2_REST:Utilities:Instance_Operations:Construct Request for Describe Instances</process-name>
        <parameters>
          <input>
            <from>access key</from>
            <to>access key</to>
          </input>
          <input>
            <from>secret key</from>
            <to>secret key</to>
          </input>
          <input>
            <from>session token</from>
            <to>session token</to>
          </input>
          <input>
            <from>region</from>
            <to>region</to>
          </input>
          <input>
            <from>instances set</from>
            <to>instances set</to>
          </input>
          <input>
            <from>filter set</from>
            <to>filter set</to>
          </input>
          <output>
            <from>adapter request</from>
            <to>adapter request</to>
          </output>
        </parameters>
        <meta>
          <documentation />
          <run-mode-handling>
            <run-mode>OCP</run-mode>
            <allow-step-into>false</allow-step-into>
          </run-mode-handling>
          <checkpoint>false</checkpoint>
        </meta>
        <location>:call-process[1]</location>
      </call-process>
      <call-process>
        <process-name>:AO-AD-Amazon_EC2_REST:Utilities:Call Amazon EC2 Adapter</process-name>
        <parameters>
          <input>
            <from>adapter name</from>
            <to>adapter name</to>
          </input>
          <input>
            <from>adapter request</from>
            <to>adapter request</to>
          </input>
          <output>
            <from>adapter response</from>
            <to>adapter response</to>
          </output>
        </parameters>
        <meta>
          <documentation />
          <run-mode-handling>
            <run-mode>OCP</run-mode>
            <allow-step-into>false</allow-step-into>
          </run-mode-handling>
          <checkpoint>false</checkpoint>
        </meta>
        <location>:call-process[2]</location>
      </call-process>
    </sequence>
    <meta>
      <expose-to>
        <consumer>RULE</consumer>
        <consumer>SCHEDULE</consumer>
      </expose-to>
      <documentation>
        <description>Returns information about instances that you own.
If you specify one or more instance IDs, Amazon EC2 returns information for those instances. If you
do not specify instance IDs, Amazon EC2 returns information for all relevant instances. If you specify
an invalid instance ID, a fault is returned. If you specify an instance that you do not own, it will not be
included in the returned results.</description>
        <version>1.0</version>
      </documentation>
      <logging-options>
        <is-enabled>false</is-enabled>
        <log-file-name></log-file-name>
      </logging-options>
      <peer-location>
        <location>any</location>
      </peer-location>
      <record-metrics>false</record-metrics>
      <process-id>8fa00a95-9db3-372b-848c-3ac6dde32cf6</process-id>
      <author>admin</author>
      <category></category>
      <status></status>
      <keywords></keywords>
      <systems></systems>
      <last-modified-by>aoadmin</last-modified-by>
      <last-modified>1609911941783</last-modified>
    </meta>
  </process-def>
</process>