<process draft="false" dev-studio-version="7.6.01.02">
  <process-def name=":AO-AD-NetAPP_Storage:v4.0:Data_Set:Find Members Of Data Set">
    <parameters>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>The name of the adapter. Default Name: NetAppActor</description>
        <from>adapter name</from>
        <to>adapter name</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="true">
        <description>Find details of members of specified dataset

Sample Items XML:

&lt;items&gt;
&lt;item&gt;
		&lt;targets&gt;
			&lt;target&gt;
				&lt;host&gt;10.10.10.10&lt;/host&gt;
				&lt;user-name&gt;userName&lt;/user-name&gt;
				&lt;password&gt;password&lt;/password&gt;
				&lt;protocol&gt;http&lt;/protocol&gt;
				&lt;port&gt;8088&lt;/port&gt;                                
			&lt;/target&gt;
		&lt;/targets&gt;
	&lt;target&gt;server1&lt;/target&gt;
	&lt;dataset-name-or-id&gt;test1&lt;/dataset-name-or-id&gt;
	&lt;include-deleted&gt;true&lt;/include-deleted&gt;
	&lt;include-exports-info&gt;true&lt;/include-exports-info&gt;
	&lt;include-indirect&gt;true&lt;/include-indirect&gt;
	&lt;include-is-available&gt;true&lt;/include-is-available&gt;
	&lt;include-space-info&gt;true&lt;/include-space-info&gt;
	&lt;suppress-status-refresh&gt;false&lt;/suppress-status-refresh&gt;
	&lt;storageset-name-or-id&gt;test1:root&lt;/storageset-name-or-id&gt;
     &lt;dp-node-name&gt;Primary data&lt;/dp-node-name&gt;
	&lt;member-name-or-id&gt;simeth0:/bmc_1/vol1&lt;/member-name-or-id&gt;
&lt;/item&gt;
&lt;/items&gt;

Parameters Description:

targets [Conditional] 

        It is parent XML element for &lt;target&gt; XML element. 
        The &lt;target&gt; XML element is used to specify dynamic targets at request level. 
        Note: The &lt;targets&gt; XML element is required if the adapter configuration is empty in Grid Manager. 

target [Conditional] 
        It is child XML element of &lt;targets&gt; XML element. This element is used to specify dynamic targets at request level. 

        Using dynamic targets you can define connection information for a remote host within an adapter request. This allows you to configure an adapter in Grid Manager, by specifying configuration information in an adapter request. 

        Note: (1) Adapter configuration specified using request level dynamic targets takes precedence over Grid Manager level configuration information. (2) If request level dynamic target is specified using &lt;targets&gt; XML element, then the &lt;target&gt; element which is child of &lt;item&gt; element is ignored. (3) This element is required if &lt;targets&gt; XML element is present in the adapter request. 

host [Conditional] 
Host name or IP address of server on which NetApp DataFabric Manager is running. 
Note: This element is required if &lt;targets&gt; XML element is present in the adapter request. 

user-name [Conditional] 
NetApp DataFabric Manager login username. 
Note: This element is required if &lt;targets&gt; XML element is present in the adapter request. 

password [Conditional] 
NetApp DataFabric Manager login password. 

You can encrypt the password by specifying the encryption type attribute. 
For example: &lt;password encryption-type = "Base64"&gt;cGFzc3dvcmQ=&lt;/password&gt;. 
Note: This element is required if &lt;targets&gt; XML element is present in the adapter request. 

protocol [Optional] 
Communication protocol used by adapter. Valid value is http or https. Default value is http. 

port [Optional] 
Port on which NetApp DataFabric Manager is enabled. Default value is 8088 for http protocol and 8488 for https protocol. 

target [Optional] 
It is child XML element of &lt;item&gt; XML element. 
You can use this element to specify the connection information for a DFM Server. For this a comma separated list of configuration names can be specified. This executes the request simultaneously on all DFM servers identified by the configuration names. 
Valid values: 
1. The values specified for &lt;target&gt; XML element must be same as the values that have been specified for the name attribute of &lt;config&gt; element in Grid Manager adapter configuration. 
2. You can provide "ALL" as the value. In this case the request will get executed on all the DFM servers defined in Grid Manager adapter configuration. 
3. You can specify multiple comma separated names to allow simultaneous execution of requests across multiple DFM servers. 
4. You can skip this element. In that case the request will be executed on the first defined Grid Manager adapter configuration. 
You can leave this element empty. In that case the request will be executed on the first defined Grid Manager adapter configuration. 

Note: This element is ignored if request level dynamic target is specified using &lt;targets&gt; XML element.



dataset-name-or-id[Required]
	Name or identifier of the data set whose members will be listed.

dp-node-name[Optional]
	List only the members in this policy node. If none is specified, then list members in all policy nodes. If both dp-node-name and storageset-name-or-id are specified, then the value of dp-node-name is ignored.

include-deleted[Optional]
	This is a boolean field. If present and true, members which are marked as deleted in the database are also returned. Otherwise, deleted members are not returned. Valid values - true,false

include-exports-info[Optional]
	This is a boolean field. If true, the export information of members is included in output. If the member is exported over NFS, the NFS export name is retuned in nfs-export-name element in dataset-member-info. If the member is exported over CIFS, the share names are returned in cifs-share-names array in dataset-member-info. In case the members are accessed using both NFS and CIFS (i.e Mixed mode) then both NFS export name and CIFS share names are returned. Default value is false.

include-indirect[Optional]
	This is a boolean field. If true, indirect members are included. By default they are not included. An example of an indirect member is a qtree in a volume which is a direct member of the data set.

include-is-available[Optional]
	This is a boolean field. If true, the is-available status is calculated for each member which may make the call to this operation take much longer. Default is false.

include-space-info[Optional]
	This is a boolean field. If true, the space status is computed for all members, the space status and detailed space conditions of every data set member is returned if the space status of the member is "warning" or "error". Default value is false.

storageset-name-or-id[Optional]
	List only the members in this storage set. If none is specified, then list members in all storagesets mapped to this data set's nodes. If both dp-node-name and storageset-name-or-id are specified, then the value of dp-node-name is ignored.

suppress-status-refresh[Optional]
	If true, do not refresh the member status. If false or omitted, the status of all members will be refreshed before being returned.

member-name-or-id[Optional]
	Name or id in the DFM database, of a specific member of the dataset. If specified, details of only this object will be returned.
</description>
        <from>items</from>
        <to>items</to>
      </input>
      <output global="false" required="false">
        <to>adapter response</to>
        <from>adapter response</from>
      </output>
    </parameters>
    <access />
    <sequence>
      <assign>
        <assignment>
          <output>
            <to>operation name</to>
            <value>find-dataset-members</value>
          </output>
        </assignment>
        <meta>
          <documentation />
          <checkpoint>false</checkpoint>
        </meta>
        <location>:assign[1]</location>
      </assign>
      <call-process>
        <process-name>:AO-AD-NetAPP_Storage:Utilities:Invoke Adapter Request</process-name>
        <parameters>
          <input>
            <from>adapter name</from>
            <to>adapter name</to>
          </input>
          <input>
            <from>items</from>
            <to>items</to>
          </input>
          <input>
            <from>operation name</from>
            <to>operation name</to>
          </input>
          <output>
            <from>adapter response</from>
            <to>adapter response</to>
          </output>
        </parameters>
        <meta>
          <documentation />
          <run-mode-handling>
            <run-mode>OCP</run-mode>
            <allow-step-into>false</allow-step-into>
          </run-mode-handling>
          <checkpoint>false</checkpoint>
        </meta>
        <after-execution>
          <console-output>
            <type>INFO</type>
            <summary>
              <concat>
                <input>
                  <value></value>
                </input>
              </concat>
            </summary>
            <detail>
              <concat>
                <input>
                  <value></value>
                </input>
              </concat>
            </detail>
          </console-output>
        </after-execution>
        <location>:call-process[1]</location>
      </call-process>
    </sequence>
    <meta>
      <expose-to>
        <consumer>RULE</consumer>
        <consumer>SCHEDULE</consumer>
      </expose-to>
      <documentation>
        <description>Find details of members of specified dataset</description>
        <version></version>
      </documentation>
      <peer-location>
        <location>any</location>
      </peer-location>
      <record-metrics>false</record-metrics>
      <process-id>1b709bf4-cb97-3330-97f8-ef5917181812</process-id>
      <author />
      <category />
      <status />
      <keywords />
      <systems />
      <last-modified-by />
      <last-modified>1290598196157</last-modified>
    </meta>
  </process-def>
</process>