<process draft="false" dev-studio-version="7.6.01.02">
  <process-def name=":AO-AD-IBM_Tivoli_Storage_Manager:v5.5:Access:Set Backup Access">
    <parameters>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>adapter name [Optional]
The name of the adapter that is enabled on the Peer.
The default adapter name is IBMTSMActor</description>
        <from>adapter name</from>
        <to>adapter name</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="true">
        <description>The set backup access command gives users at other nodes access to your backup files. You can give another user access to a specific file or image, multiple files or images, or all files in a directory. When you give access to another user, that user can restore or retrieve your objects.

Sample Request XML:

&lt;items&gt;
  &lt;item&gt;
  &lt;operation-name&gt;set-backup-access&lt;/operation-name&gt;
  &lt;timeout-secs&gt;120&lt;/timeout-secs&gt;
&lt;command-arguments&gt;
      &lt;filespec&gt;C:\YServer.txt&lt;/filespec&gt;
      &lt;nodename&gt;l-16862&lt;/nodename&gt;
    &lt;/command-arguments&gt;
  &lt;/item&gt;
&lt;/items&gt;

Parameters Description:

Command Arguments Description

filespec[Required]
	Specifies the path, file, image, or directory to which your are giving access to another node or user. Use wildcard characters to specify a group of files or images, or all files in a directory; all objects in a directory branch; or all objects in a drive. However, you cannot use a wildcard to specify all drives. Use a single asterisk "*" for the file spec to give access to all files or images owned by you and backed up on the server. When the command set access backup "*" node is entered, no check is made with the server; it is assumed you have at least one object backed up.

If you give access to a branch of the current working directory, you only need to specify the branch. If you give access to objects that are not in a branch of the current working directory, you must specify the complete path. The file spec to which you gave access must have at least one backup version or archive copy object (file or directory) on the
server.

To specify all files in a named directory, enter d:\test\mine\proj1\* on the command line.

To give access to all objects below a certain level, use an asterisk, directory delimiter, and an asterisk at the end of your file spec. For example, to give access to all objects

nodename[Required]
	Specifies the client node of the user to whom you are giving access. Use wildcards to give access to more than one node with similar node names. Use an asterisk (*) to give access to all nodes.</description>
        <from>items</from>
        <to>items</to>
      </input>
      <output global="false" required="false">
        <to>adapter response</to>
        <from>adapter response</from>
      </output>
    </parameters>
    <access />
    <sequence>
      <call-process>
        <process-name>:AO-AD-IBM_Tivoli_Storage_Manager:Utilities:Execute Request</process-name>
        <parameters>
          <input>
            <from>adapter name</from>
            <to>adapter name</to>
          </input>
          <input>
            <from>items</from>
            <to>items</to>
          </input>
          <input>
            <value>set-backup-access</value>
            <to>valid operation name</to>
          </input>
          <output>
            <from>adapter response</from>
            <to>adapter response</to>
          </output>
        </parameters>
        <meta>
          <documentation />
          <run-mode-handling>
            <run-mode>OCP</run-mode>
            <allow-step-into>false</allow-step-into>
          </run-mode-handling>
          <checkpoint>false</checkpoint>
        </meta>
        <location>:call-process[1]</location>
      </call-process>
    </sequence>
    <meta>
      <expose-to>
        <consumer>RULE</consumer>
        <consumer>SCHEDULE</consumer>
      </expose-to>
      <documentation>
        <description>This wrapper is used to give users at other nodes access to your backup files. You can give another user access to a specific file or image, multiple files or images, or all files in a directory. When you give access to another user, that user can restore or retrieve your objects.</description>
        <version></version>
      </documentation>
      <peer-location>
        <location>any</location>
      </peer-location>
      <record-metrics>false</record-metrics>
      <process-id>19b95300-82d1-33c3-9099-80f86ba97d52</process-id>
      <author />
      <category />
      <status />
      <keywords />
      <systems />
      <last-modified-by />
      <last-modified>1290597030173</last-modified>
    </meta>
  </process-def>
</process>