<process draft="false" dev-studio-version="7.6.01.02">
  <process-def name=":AO-AD-IBM_Tivoli_Storage_Manager:v5.5:Group:Delete Group">
    <parameters>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>adapter name [Optional]
The name of the adapter that is enabled on the Peer.
The default adapter name is IBMTSMActor</description>
        <from>adapter name</from>
        <to>adapter name</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="true">
        <description>Delete group command is used to delete a group backup on the Tivoli Storage Manager server.

Sample Request XML:

&lt;items&gt;
  &lt;item&gt;
&lt;operation-name&gt;delete-group&lt;/operation-name&gt;
  &lt;timeout-secs&gt;120&lt;/timeout-secs&gt;
    &lt;command-options&gt;
      &lt;pitdate&gt;10/01/2008&lt;/pitdate&gt;
      &lt;pittime&gt;15:02:04&lt;/pittime&gt;
      &lt;noprompt /&gt;
    &lt;/command-options&gt;
    &lt;command-arguments&gt;
      &lt;filespec&gt;\testfs\testgroup2&lt;/filespec&gt;
    &lt;/command-arguments&gt;
  &lt;/item&gt;
&lt;/items&gt;

Parameters Description:

Command Arguments Description:

filespec[Required]
	Specifies the virtual file space name (enclosed in braces) and the group name on the server that you want to query.

Command Options Description:

fromnode[Optional]
	The fromnode option permits one node to perform commands for another node. A user on another node must use the set access command to permit you to query, restore, or retrieve files or images for the other node.
	
inactive[Optional]
	Use the inactive option to display both active and inactive objects:	
	
pitdate[Optional]
	Use the pitdate option with the pittime option to establish a point in time for which you want to display or restore the latest version of your backups. Files or images that were backed up on or before the date and time you specified, and which were not deleted before the date and time you specified, are processed. Backup versions that you create after this date and time are ignored.
Note: When pitdate is used, the inactive option is implicit.

pittime[Optional]
	Use the pittime option with the pitdate option to establish a point in time for which you want to display or restore the latest version of your backups. Files or images that were backed up on or before the date and time you specify, and which were not deleted before the date and time you specify, are processed. Backup versions that you create after this date and time are ignored. This option is ignored if you do not specify pitdate option.
Note: The PITTIME option cannot be used without specifying the PITDATE option

noprompt[Optional]              
	The noprompt option suppresses the confirmation prompt that is presented by the delete group, delete archive, expire, restore image, and set event commands.  
Note: Although this tag is optional but user must provide this tag otherwise application might prompt the user in which case the adapter will hang and time out after a specifc time period.</description>
        <from>items</from>
        <to>items</to>
      </input>
      <output global="false" required="false">
        <to>adapter response</to>
        <from>adapter response</from>
      </output>
    </parameters>
    <access />
    <sequence>
      <call-process>
        <process-name>:AO-AD-IBM_Tivoli_Storage_Manager:Utilities:Execute Request</process-name>
        <parameters>
          <input>
            <from>adapter name</from>
            <to>adapter name</to>
          </input>
          <input>
            <from>items</from>
            <to>items</to>
          </input>
          <input>
            <value>delete-group</value>
            <to>valid operation name</to>
          </input>
          <output>
            <from>adapter response</from>
            <to>adapter response</to>
          </output>
        </parameters>
        <meta>
          <documentation />
          <run-mode-handling>
            <run-mode>OCP</run-mode>
            <allow-step-into>false</allow-step-into>
          </run-mode-handling>
          <checkpoint>false</checkpoint>
        </meta>
        <location>:call-process[1]</location>
      </call-process>
    </sequence>
    <meta>
      <expose-to>
        <consumer>RULE</consumer>
        <consumer>SCHEDULE</consumer>
      </expose-to>
      <documentation>
        <description>Delete group command is used to delete a group backup on the Tivoli Storage Manager server.</description>
        <version></version>
      </documentation>
      <peer-location>
        <location>any</location>
      </peer-location>
      <record-metrics>false</record-metrics>
      <process-id>00729261-0fd9-34fe-b9eb-c7d741b9b73f</process-id>
      <author />
      <category />
      <status />
      <keywords />
      <systems />
      <last-modified-by />
      <last-modified>1290597036526</last-modified>
    </meta>
  </process-def>
</process>