<process draft="false" dev-studio-version="7.6.01.02">
  <process-def name=":AO-AD-IBM_Tivoli_Storage_Manager:Adapter_Action_Input_Constructors:v5.5:Backup:Backup Incremental">
    <parameters>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>The autofsrename option renames an existing file space that is not Unicode-enabled on the Tivoli Storage Manager server so that a Unicode-enabled file space with the original name can be created for the current operation. 
Valid values – Yes, No</description>
        <from>autofsrename</from>
        <to>autofsrename</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>The changingretries option specifies how many additional times you want the client to attempt to back up or archive a file that is in use. Valid values-number</description>
        <from>changingretries</from>
        <to>changingretries</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>The compressalways option specifies whether to continue compressing an object if it grows during compression. 
Valid values-Yes, No.
Default value - Yes</description>
        <from>compressalways</from>
        <to>compressalways</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>The compression option compresses files before you send them to the server.Valid values - yes,no(default)</description>
        <from>compression</from>
        <to>compression</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>The dirsonly option processes directories only. The client does not process files.
Valid values-true,false</description>
        <from>dirsonly</from>
        <to>dirsonly</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>The Tivoli Storage Manager client opens the file you specify with this option and processes the list of files within according to the specific command. With the exception of the restore and retrieve commands, when you use the filelist option, Tivoli Storage Manager ignores all other file specifications on the command line.
Note: The &lt;FILELIST&gt; option does not support the wildcard characters.</description>
        <from>filelist</from>
        <to>filelist</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>The filesonly option restricts backup, restore, retrieve, or query processing to files only. You cannot restore or retrieve directories from the Tivoli Storage Manager server when using the filesonly option with the restore or retrieve commands. However,
directories with default attributes are created, if required, as placeholders for files that you restore or retrieve
Valid values-true,false</description>
        <from>filesonly</from>
        <to>filesonly</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>Any application that touches a file can implicitly cause that file's last access date to change to the time that the application touches it. This is a function of the file system, not the application. Because of this, when the client backs up or archives a file, it can trigger an update to the file's last access date. This can cause problems for other applications such as Storage Resource Management (SRM), whose processing relies on accurate last access dates.

Use the preservelastaccessdate option during a backup or archive operation to specify whether to reset the last access date of any specified files to their original value following the backup or archive operation. By default, the Tivoli Storage Manager client will not reset the last access date of any backed up or archived files to their original value following the backup or archive operation. This option requires extra processing time during backup and archive for each file that is sent to the Tivoli Storage Manager server, so it should only be enabled when necessary. If you have enabled open file support, the last access date for files will always be preserved regardless of the setting for preservelastaccessdate. When using open file support, leave this option disabled.
Valid values – Yes, No
Default value - No
</description>
        <from>preservelastaccessdate</from>
        <to>preservelastaccessdate</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>The skipntpermissions option bypasses processing of NTFS security information. Select this option for incremental backups, selective backups, archives, retrieves and restores. 
Valid values-yes,no
Default value-no
</description>
        <from>skipntpermissions</from>
        <to>skipntpermissions</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>The skipntsecuritycrc option controls the computation of the security cyclic redundancy check (CRC) for a comparison of NTFS security information during an incremental or selective backup, archive, restore, or retrieve operation. If you set the skipntsecuritycrc option to no (the default), performance might be slower because the program must retrieve all the security descriptors.  
Valid values-yes,no
Default value-no
</description>
        <from>skipntsecuritycrc</from>
        <to>skipntsecuritycrc</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>Use the snapshotroot option with the incremental, selective, or archive commands in conjunction with a third-party application that provides a snapshot of a logical volume, to associate the data on the local snapshot with the real file space data that is stored on the Tivoli Storage Manager server.</description>
        <from>snapshotroot</from>
        <to>snapshotroot</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>The subdir option specifies whether you want to include subdirectories of named directories for processing. Valid values-yes,no
Note: SUBDIR is not a valid option when using FILELIST option.
</description>
        <from>subdir</from>
        <to>subdir</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>Specifies the path and file name that you want to back up. Use wildcards to select a group of files or all the files in a directory. You can specify as many file specifications as available resources or other operating system limits permit. Separate file specifications with a space. You can also use the filelist option to process a list of files. The Tivoli Storage Manager client opens the file you specify with this option and processes the list of files within according to the specific command. If you do not specify a file specification, the default domain or the domain specified as an option is backed up.

If you specify a file system, all new and changed files are backed up. In addition, the last incremental date for the file space is updated on the server. If you specify a file or directory, the last incremental date is not updated. This means the file or directory might be backed up again if a later backup is performed using the incrbydate option.

If you specify a file system, specify the file system without a trailing slash.</description>
        <from>filespec</from>
        <to>filespec</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>The timeout value is seconds. This is the time after which the command will timeout regardless of whether the command execution is complete or not.</description>
        <from>timeout secs</from>
        <to>timeout secs</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>The domain option specifies the drives that you want to include for incremental backup in your client domain.</description>
        <from>domain</from>
        <to>domain</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>Use the incrbydate option with the incremental command to back up new and changed files with a modification date later than the last incremental backup stored at the server, unless you exclude the file from backup. Files added at the client after the last
incremental backup, but with a modification date earlier than the last incremental, are not backed up.
Valid values-true,false</description>
        <from>incrbydate</from>
        <to>incrbydate</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>The memoryefficientbackup option specifies the memory-conserving algorithm to use for processing full file space backups. One method backs up one directory at a time, using less memory. The other method uses much less memory, but requires more disk space.
Valid values - No
   Your client node uses the faster, more memory-intensive method when processing incremental backups. This is the default.

Yes
   Your client node uses the method that requires less memory when processing incremental backups.

Diskcachemethod
   Your client node uses the method that requires much less memory but more disk space when processing incremental backups for full file systems.

Default value – No</description>
        <from>memoryefficientbackup</from>
        <to>memoryefficientbackup</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>Use the nojournal option with the incremental command to specify that you want to perform a traditional full incremental backup, instead of the default journal-based backup.

Journal-based incremental backup differs from the traditional full incremental backup in the following ways:

*  Tivoli Storage Manager does not enforce non-default copy frequencies (other than 0).
*  Attribute changes to an object require a back up of the entire object.
</description>
        <from>nojournal</from>
        <to>nojournal</to>
      </input>
      <output global="false" required="false">
        <to>items</to>
        <from>final items</from>
      </output>
    </parameters>
    <access />
    <sequence>
      <assign>
        <assignment>
          <output>
            <to>final items</to>
            <value>
              <root />
            </value>
          </output>
          <xslt-stylesheet>
            <stylesheet-replacement-tokens>
              <replacement-token name="changingretries">
                <input global="false">
                  <from>changingretries</from>
                </input>
              </replacement-token>
              <replacement-token name="compressalways">
                <input global="false">
                  <from>compressalways</from>
                </input>
              </replacement-token>
              <replacement-token name="compression">
                <input global="false">
                  <from>compression</from>
                </input>
              </replacement-token>
              <replacement-token name="dirsonly">
                <input global="false">
                  <from>dirsonly</from>
                </input>
              </replacement-token>
              <replacement-token name="filelist">
                <input global="false">
                  <from>filelist</from>
                </input>
              </replacement-token>
              <replacement-token name="filesonly">
                <input global="false">
                  <from>filesonly</from>
                </input>
              </replacement-token>
              <replacement-token name="filespec">
                <input global="false">
                  <from>filespec</from>
                </input>
              </replacement-token>
              <replacement-token name="preservelastaccessdate">
                <input global="false">
                  <from>preservelastaccessdate</from>
                </input>
              </replacement-token>
              <replacement-token name="skipntpermissions">
                <input global="false">
                  <from>skipntpermissions</from>
                </input>
              </replacement-token>
              <replacement-token name="skipntsecuritycrc">
                <input global="false">
                  <from>skipntsecuritycrc</from>
                </input>
              </replacement-token>
              <replacement-token name="snapshotroot">
                <input global="false">
                  <from>snapshotroot</from>
                </input>
              </replacement-token>
              <replacement-token name="subdir">
                <input global="false">
                  <from>subdir</from>
                </input>
              </replacement-token>
              <replacement-token name="timeout secs">
                <input global="false">
                  <from>timeout secs</from>
                </input>
              </replacement-token>
              <replacement-token name="autofsrename">
                <input global="false">
                  <from>autofsrename</from>
                </input>
              </replacement-token>
              <replacement-token name="domain">
                <input global="false">
                  <from>domain</from>
                </input>
              </replacement-token>
              <replacement-token name="memoryefficientbackup">
                <input global="false">
                  <from>memoryefficientbackup</from>
                </input>
              </replacement-token>
              <replacement-token name="nojournal">
                <input global="false">
                  <from>nojournal</from>
                </input>
              </replacement-token>
              <replacement-token name="incrbydate">
                <input global="false">
                  <from>incrbydate</from>
                </input>
              </replacement-token>
            </stylesheet-replacement-tokens>
            <stylesheet><![CDATA[<xsl:stylesheet xmlns:xsl="http://www.w3.org/1999/XSL/Transform" version="1.0">
  <xsl:output indent="no" omit-xml-declaration="yes" />
  <xsl:template match="/">
    <items>
      <item>
        <operation-name>
          <xsl:text disable-output-escaping="no">backup-incremental</xsl:text>
        </operation-name>
        <xsl:if test="string('${timeout secs}')!=''">
          <timeout-secs>
            <xsl:value-of select="'${timeout secs}'" disable-output-escaping="no" />
          </timeout-secs>
        </xsl:if>
        <command-options>
          <xsl:if test="string('${changingretries}')!=''">
            <changingretries>
              <xsl:value-of select="'${changingretries}'" disable-output-escaping="no" />
            </changingretries>
          </xsl:if>
          <xsl:if test="string('${compressalways}')!=''">
            <compressalways>
              <xsl:value-of select="'${compressalways}'" disable-output-escaping="no" />
            </compressalways>
          </xsl:if>
          <xsl:if test="string('${compression}')!=''">
            <compression>
              <xsl:value-of select="'${compression}'" disable-output-escaping="no" />
            </compression>
          </xsl:if>
          <xsl:if test="string('${dirsonly}')='true'">
            <dirsonly />
          </xsl:if>
          <xsl:if test="string('${filelist}')!=''">
            <filelist>
              <xsl:value-of select="'${filelist}'" disable-output-escaping="no" />
            </filelist>
          </xsl:if>
          <xsl:if test="string('${filesonly}')='true'">
            <filesonly />
          </xsl:if>
          <xsl:if test="string('${preservelastaccessdate}')!=''">
            <preservelastaccessdate>
              <xsl:value-of select="'${preservelastaccessdate}'" disable-output-escaping="no" />
            </preservelastaccessdate>
          </xsl:if>
          <xsl:if test="string('${skipntpermissions}')!=''">
            <skipntpermissions>
              <xsl:value-of select="'${skipntpermissions}'" disable-output-escaping="no" />
            </skipntpermissions>
          </xsl:if>
          <xsl:if test="string('${skipntsecuritycrc}')!=''">
            <skipntsecuritycrc>
              <xsl:value-of select="'${skipntsecuritycrc}'" disable-output-escaping="no" />
            </skipntsecuritycrc>
          </xsl:if>
          <xsl:if test="string('${snapshotroot}')!=''">
            <snapshotroot>
              <xsl:value-of select="'${snapshotroot}'" disable-output-escaping="no" />
            </snapshotroot>
          </xsl:if>
          <xsl:if test="string('${subdir}')!=''">
            <subdir>
              <xsl:value-of select="'${subdir}'" disable-output-escaping="no" />
            </subdir>
          </xsl:if>
          <xsl:if test="string('${autofsrename}')!=''">
            <autofsrename>
              <xsl:value-of select="'${autofsrename}'" disable-output-escaping="no" />
            </autofsrename>
          </xsl:if>
          <xsl:if test="string('${domain}')!=''">
            <domain>
              <xsl:value-of select="'${domain}'" disable-output-escaping="no" />
            </domain>
          </xsl:if>
          <xsl:if test="string('${memoryefficientbackup}')!=''">
            <memoryefficientbackup>
              <xsl:value-of select="'${memoryefficientbackup}'" disable-output-escaping="no" />
            </memoryefficientbackup>
          </xsl:if>
          <xsl:if test="string('${nojournal}')!=''">
            <nojournal>
              <xsl:value-of select="'${nojournal}'" disable-output-escaping="no" />
            </nojournal>
          </xsl:if>
          <xsl:if test="string('${incrbydate}')='true'">
            <incrbydate />
          </xsl:if>
        </command-options>
        <command-arguments>
          <xsl:if test="string('${filespec}')!=''">
            <filespec>
              <xsl:value-of select="'${filespec}'" disable-output-escaping="no" />
            </filespec>
          </xsl:if>
        </command-arguments>
      </item>
    </items>
  </xsl:template>
</xsl:stylesheet>]]></stylesheet>
          </xslt-stylesheet>
        </assignment>
        <meta>
          <documentation />
          <checkpoint>false</checkpoint>
        </meta>
        <after-execution>
          <log>
            <level>debug</level>
            <parameters>
              <input>
                <value>FINAL ITEMS: </value>
              </input>
              <input>
                <from>final items</from>
              </input>
            </parameters>
          </log>
        </after-execution>
        <location>:assign[1]</location>
      </assign>
    </sequence>
    <meta>
      <expose-to>
        <consumer>RULE</consumer>
        <consumer>SCHEDULE</consumer>
      </expose-to>
      <documentation>
        <description>Utility to create items xml for Backup Incremental process.</description>
        <version></version>
      </documentation>
      <peer-location>
        <location>any</location>
      </peer-location>
      <record-metrics>false</record-metrics>
      <process-id>423bd891-08c5-398a-af66-69a1a0abe231</process-id>
      <author />
      <category />
      <status />
      <keywords />
      <systems />
      <last-modified-by />
      <last-modified>1290596958182</last-modified>
    </meta>
  </process-def>
</process>