<process draft="false" dev-studio-version="7.6.01.02">
  <process-def name=":AO-AD-NetAPP_Storage:v4.0:Job:Find Job Events">
    <parameters>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>The name of the adapter. Default Name: NetAppActor</description>
        <from>adapter name</from>
        <to>adapter name</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="true">
        <description>Finds the details of all the job progress events that match the filter criteria specified.

Sample Items XML:

&lt;items&gt;
	&lt;item&gt;
		&lt;targets&gt;
			&lt;target&gt;
				&lt;host&gt;10.10.10.10&lt;/host&gt;
				&lt;user-name&gt;userName&lt;/user-name&gt;
				&lt;password&gt;password&lt;/password&gt;
				&lt;protocol&gt;http&lt;/protocol&gt;
				&lt;port&gt;8088&lt;/port&gt;                                
			&lt;/target&gt;
		&lt;/targets&gt;
		&lt;target&gt;server1&lt;/target&gt;
		&lt;end-time&gt;1280918644&lt;/end-time&gt;
		&lt;history&gt;FALSE&lt;/history&gt;
		&lt;job-id&gt;123456&lt;/job-id&gt;
		&lt;job-types&gt;
			&lt;job-type&gt;provision_member&lt;/job-type&gt;
		&lt;/job-types&gt;
		&lt;object-name-or-id&gt;testds2&lt;/object-name-or-id&gt;
		&lt;start-time&gt;1233485107&lt;/start-time&gt;
	&lt;/item&gt;
&lt;/items&gt;

Parameters Description:

targets [Conditional] 

        It is parent XML element for &lt;target&gt; XML element. 
        The &lt;target&gt; XML element is used to specify dynamic targets at request level. 
        Note: The &lt;targets&gt; XML element is required if the adapter configuration is empty in Grid Manager. 

target [Conditional] 
        It is child XML element of &lt;targets&gt; XML element. This element is used to specify dynamic targets at request level. 

        Using dynamic targets you can define connection information for a remote host within an adapter request. This allows you to configure an adapter in Grid Manager, by specifying configuration information in an adapter request. 

        Note: (1) Adapter configuration specified using request level dynamic targets takes precedence over Grid Manager level configuration information. (2) If request level dynamic target is specified using &lt;targets&gt; XML element, then the &lt;target&gt; element which is child of &lt;item&gt; element is ignored. (3) This element is required if &lt;targets&gt; XML element is present in the adapter request. 

host [Conditional] 
Host name or IP address of server on which NetApp DataFabric Manager is running. 
Note: This element is required if &lt;targets&gt; XML element is present in the adapter request. 

user-name [Conditional] 
NetApp DataFabric Manager login username. 
Note: This element is required if &lt;targets&gt; XML element is present in the adapter request. 

password [Conditional] 
NetApp DataFabric Manager login password. 

You can encrypt the password by specifying the encryption type attribute. 
For example: &lt;password encryption-type = "Base64"&gt;cGFzc3dvcmQ=&lt;/password&gt;. 
Note: This element is required if &lt;targets&gt; XML element is present in the adapter request. 

protocol [Optional] 
Communication protocol used by adapter. Valid value is http or https. Default value is http. 

port [Optional] 
Port on which NetApp DataFabric Manager is enabled. Default value is 8088 for http protocol and 8488 for https protocol. 

target [Optional] 
It is child XML element of &lt;item&gt; XML element. 
You can use this element to specify the connection information for a DFM Server. For this a comma separated list of configuration names can be specified. This executes the request simultaneously on all DFM servers identified by the configuration names. 
Valid values: 
1. The values specified for &lt;target&gt; XML element must be same as the values that have been specified for the name attribute of &lt;config&gt; element in Grid Manager adapter configuration. 
2. You can provide "ALL" as the value. In this case the request will get executed on all the DFM servers defined in Grid Manager adapter configuration. 
3. You can specify multiple comma separated names to allow simultaneous execution of requests across multiple DFM servers. 
4. You can skip this element. In that case the request will be executed on the first defined Grid Manager adapter configuration. 
You can leave this element empty. In that case the request will be executed on the first defined Grid Manager adapter configuration. 

Note: This element is ignored if request level dynamic target is specified using &lt;targets&gt; XML element.


end-time[Optional]
	End timestamp. Events after this time will not be returned. If not present, all events up to the present are returned. The input value is seconds since 1/1/1970 in UTC. Range: [0..2^31-1].

history[Optional]
	If FALSE return only the most recent progress events for job. The most recent progress events define the current progress of the job. For example a backup job generates a job-progress event which says "Retrieving preferred interfaces" and then when the interfaces are retrieved it generates an event "Retrieved preferred interfaces", the earlier then moves to history. The latter one becomes the current event. If TRUE all the events are returned. Default value is FALSE.

job-id[Optional]
	Identifier of the job to list progress events for. Only object-name-or-id or job-id may be supplied, but not both. If neither is supplied, all progress events are returned. Range: [1..2^31-1]. 

job-types[Optional]
	This parent tag lists job types associated with the progress events. Only progress events of jobs of these job types are listed. If not specified, progress events for all job types are returned. Only one of job-type or job-types can be specified. Job types may be specified in &lt;job-type&gt; tags inside this parent tag.

job-type[Optional]
	This contains individual job type which is associated with the progress event. This is a child tag of the &lt;job-types&gt; tag. 

object-name-or-id[Optional]
	Identifier of the object to list progress events for. If not specified, progress events for all jobs are returned. Only object-name-or-id or job-id may be supplied, but not both.

start-time[Optional]
	Start timestamp. Events before this time will not be returned. If not present, all events since the earliest event are returned. The input value is seconds since 1/1/1970 in UTC. Range: [0..2^31-1].</description>
        <from>items</from>
        <to>items</to>
      </input>
      <output global="false" required="false">
        <to>adapter response</to>
        <from>adapter response</from>
      </output>
    </parameters>
    <access />
    <sequence>
      <assign>
        <assignment>
          <output>
            <to>operation name</to>
            <value>find-job-events</value>
          </output>
        </assignment>
        <meta>
          <documentation />
          <checkpoint>false</checkpoint>
        </meta>
        <location>:assign[1]</location>
      </assign>
      <call-process>
        <process-name>:AO-AD-NetAPP_Storage:Utilities:Invoke Adapter Request</process-name>
        <parameters>
          <input>
            <from>adapter name</from>
            <to>adapter name</to>
          </input>
          <input>
            <from>items</from>
            <to>items</to>
          </input>
          <input>
            <from>operation name</from>
            <to>operation name</to>
          </input>
          <output>
            <from>adapter response</from>
            <to>adapter response</to>
          </output>
        </parameters>
        <meta>
          <documentation />
          <run-mode-handling>
            <run-mode>OCP</run-mode>
            <allow-step-into>false</allow-step-into>
          </run-mode-handling>
          <checkpoint>false</checkpoint>
        </meta>
        <after-execution>
          <console-output>
            <type>INFO</type>
            <summary>
              <concat>
                <input>
                  <value></value>
                </input>
              </concat>
            </summary>
            <detail>
              <concat>
                <input>
                  <value></value>
                </input>
              </concat>
            </detail>
          </console-output>
        </after-execution>
        <location>:call-process[1]</location>
      </call-process>
    </sequence>
    <meta>
      <expose-to>
        <consumer>RULE</consumer>
        <consumer>SCHEDULE</consumer>
      </expose-to>
      <documentation>
        <description>Finds the details of all the job progress events.</description>
        <version></version>
      </documentation>
      <peer-location>
        <location>any</location>
      </peer-location>
      <record-metrics>false</record-metrics>
      <process-id>11375a39-522b-384e-b4dc-559551a842da</process-id>
      <author />
      <category />
      <status />
      <keywords />
      <systems />
      <last-modified-by />
      <last-modified>1290598207172</last-modified>
    </meta>
  </process-def>
</process>