<process draft="false" dev-studio-version="7.6.01.02">
  <process-def name=":AO-AD-IBM_Tivoli_Storage_Manager:v5.5:Archive:Delete Archive">
    <parameters>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>adapter name [Optional]
The name of the adapter that is enabled on the Peer.
The default adapter name is IBMTSMActor</description>
        <from>adapter name</from>
        <to>adapter name</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="true">
        <description>1. Deletes archived files from Tivoli Storage Manager server storage.

Sample Request XML:

&lt;items&gt;
  &lt;item&gt;
  &lt;operation-name&gt;delete-archive&lt;/operation-name&gt;
    &lt;timeout-secs&gt;120&lt;/timeout-secs&gt;
    &lt;command-options&gt;
		&lt;description&gt;"Test Description"&lt;/description&gt;
		&lt;filelist&gt;C:\filelist.txt&lt;/filelist&gt;
		&lt;dateformat&gt;DD-MM-YYYY&lt;/dateformat&gt;
&lt;numberformat&gt;d,ddd,dd&lt;/numberformat&gt;
&lt;timeformat&gt;HH,MM,SS&lt;/timeformat&gt;
&lt;noprompt/ &gt;
&lt;subdir&gt;yes&lt;/subdir&gt;
    &lt;/command-options&gt;
  &lt;/item&gt;
&lt;/items&gt;

Parameters Description:

Command Arguments Description:

filespec[Optional]
	Specifies the path and file name that you want to delete from storage. Use wildcard characters to specify a group of files or all files in a directory. You can specify as many file specifications as available resources or other operating system limits permit. Separate file specifications with a space. You can also use the filelist option to process a list of files.

Command Options Description:
	
dateformat[Optional]
	The dateformat option specifies the format you want to use to display dates. Valid values - MM/DD/YYYY, DD-MM-YYYY, DD.MM.YYYY, YYYY.MM.DD, YYYY-MM-DD		

description[Optional]
	The description option assigns or specifies a description for files when performing archive, delete archive, retrieve, query archive, or query backupset.
		
filelist[Optional]
	The Tivoli Storage Manager client opens the file you specify with this option and processes the list of files within according to the specific command. With the exception of the restore and retrieve commands, when you use the filelist option, Tivoli Storage Manager ignores all other file specifications on the command line.
Note: The &lt;FILELIST&gt; option does not support the wildcard characters.
	
subdir[Optional]
	The subdir option specifies whether you want to include subdirectories of named directories for processing. Valid values-yes,no         
Note: SUBDIR is not a valid option when using FILELIST option.

noprompt[Optional]              
	The noprompt option suppresses the confirmation prompt that is presented by the delete group, delete archive, expire, restore image, and set event commands.  
Note: Although this tag is optional but user must provide this tag otherwise application might prompt the user in which case the adapter will hang and time out after a specifc time period.

numberformat[Optional]
	The numberformat option specifies the format you want to use to display numbers. Valid values – 
1. d,ddd.dd
2. d,ddd,dd
3. d ddd,dd
4. d ddd.dd
5. d.ddd,dd
6. d'ddd,dd	

timeformat[Optional]
	The timeformat option specifies the format in which you want to display system time. Valid values – 1) HH:MM:SS 2) HH,MM,SS 3)HH.MM.SS 4) hh:mm:ssAM/PM

NOTE: Either one of “filespec” or “filelist” should be provided.
</description>
        <from>items</from>
        <to>items</to>
      </input>
      <output global="false" required="false">
        <to>adapter response</to>
        <from>adapter response</from>
      </output>
    </parameters>
    <access />
    <sequence>
      <call-process>
        <process-name>:AO-AD-IBM_Tivoli_Storage_Manager:Utilities:Execute Request</process-name>
        <parameters>
          <input>
            <from>adapter name</from>
            <to>adapter name</to>
          </input>
          <input>
            <from>items</from>
            <to>items</to>
          </input>
          <input>
            <value>delete-archive</value>
            <to>valid operation name</to>
          </input>
          <output>
            <from>adapter response</from>
            <to>adapter response</to>
          </output>
        </parameters>
        <meta>
          <documentation />
          <run-mode-handling>
            <run-mode>OCP</run-mode>
            <allow-step-into>false</allow-step-into>
          </run-mode-handling>
          <checkpoint>false</checkpoint>
        </meta>
        <location>:call-process[1]</location>
      </call-process>
    </sequence>
    <meta>
      <expose-to>
        <consumer>RULE</consumer>
        <consumer>SCHEDULE</consumer>
      </expose-to>
      <documentation>
        <description>This wrapper deletes archived files from Tivoli Storage Manager server storage.</description>
        <version></version>
      </documentation>
      <peer-location>
        <location>any</location>
      </peer-location>
      <record-metrics>false</record-metrics>
      <process-id>07b663fa-a1ec-3ccb-8732-aa815ff93744</process-id>
      <author />
      <category />
      <status />
      <keywords />
      <systems />
      <last-modified-by />
      <last-modified>1290597030753</last-modified>
    </meta>
  </process-def>
</process>