<process draft="false" dev-studio-version="7.6.01.02">
  <process-def name=":AO-AD-IBM_Tivoli_Storage_Manager:v5.5:Archive:Retrieve">
    <parameters>
      <input global="false" required="false">
        <description>adapter name [Optional]
The name of the adapter that is enabled on the Peer.
The default adapter name is IBMTSMActor</description>
        <from>adapter name</from>
        <to>adapter name</to>
      </input>
      <input global="false" required="true">
        <description>The retrieve command obtains copies of archived files from the Tivoli Storage Manager server. You can retrieve specific files or entire directories.

Sample Request XML:

&lt;items&gt;
  &lt;item&gt;
  &lt;operation-name&gt;retrieve&lt;/operation-name&gt;
    &lt;timeout-secs&gt;120&lt;/timeout-secs&gt;
				&lt;command-options&gt;
					&lt;description&gt;"Test Description"&lt;/description&gt;
					&lt;dateformat&gt;DD-MM-YYYY&lt;/dateformat&gt;
					&lt;timeformat&gt;HH,MM,SS&lt;/timeformat&gt;
					&lt;fromdate&gt;30-09-2008&lt;/fromdate&gt;
					&lt;fromtime&gt;12,00,00&lt;/fromtime&gt;
					&lt;todate&gt;01-10-2008&lt;/todate&gt;
					&lt;totime&gt;16,00,00&lt;/totime&gt;
					&lt;filesonly/&gt;
					&lt;preservepath&gt;complete&lt;/preservepath&gt;
					&lt;replace&gt;yes&lt;/replace&gt;
					&lt;skipntpermissions&gt;yes&lt;/skipntpermissions&gt;
				&lt;/command-options&gt;
				&lt;command-arguments&gt;
					&lt;source-filespec&gt;C:\tmuninst.ini&lt;/source-filespec&gt;
					&lt;dest-filespec&gt;C:\temp\&lt;/dest-filespec&gt;
				&lt;/command-arguments&gt;
  &lt;/item&gt;
&lt;/items&gt;

Parameters Description:

Command Arguments Description:

source-filespec [Optional]
	Specifies the path and file name that you want to retrieve. Use wildcard characters to specify a group of files or all the files in a directory.

dest-filespec [Optional]
	Specifies the path and file name where you want the files to reside. If you do not specify a destination, Tivoli Storage Manager restores the files to the original source path.

When entering the destinationfilespec please consider the following:

*  If the sourcefilespec names a single file, the destinationfilespec can be a file or a directory. The destinationfilespec must with a directory delimiter (\).
*  If the sourcefilespec is wildcarded or you specify the subdir=yes option, the destinationfilespec must be a directory and end with a directory delimiter (\).

Note: If the destination path or any part of it does not exist,
      Tivoli Storage Manager will create it.

Command Options Description:
	
dateformat[Optional]
	The dateformat option specifies the format you want to use to display dates. Valid values - MM/DD/YYYY, DD-MM-YYYY, DD.MM.YYYY, YYYY.MM.DD, YYYY-MM-DD		

description[Optional]
	The description option assigns or specifies a description for files when performing archive, delete archive, retrieve, query archive, or query backupset.
		
filelist[Optional]
	The Tivoli Storage Manager client opens the file you specify with this option and processes the list of files within according to the specific command. With the exception of the restore and retrieve commands, when you use the filelist option, Tivoli Storage Manager ignores all other file specifications on the command line.
Note: The &lt;FILELIST&gt; option does not support the wildcard characters.
	
timeformat[Optional]
	The timeformat option specifies the format in which you want to display system time. Valid values – 1) HH:MM:SS 2) HH,MM,SS 3)HH.MM.SS 4) hh:mm:ssAM/PM

filesonly[Optional]
	The filesonly option restricts backup, restore, retrieve, or query processing to files only. You cannot restore or retrieve directories from the Tivoli Storage Manager server when using the filesonly option with the restore or retrieve commands. However, directories with default attributes are created, if required, as placeholders for files that you restore or retrieve.

fromdate[Optional]
	Use the fromdate option with the fromtime option to specify a date and time from which you want to search for backups or archives during a restore, retrieve, or query operation. Files that were backed up or archived before this date and time are not included, although older directories might be included, if necessary, to restore or retrieve the files.

fromtime[Optional]
	Use the fromtime option with the fromdate option to specify a beginning time from which you want to search for backups or archives during a restore, retrieve, or query operation. Tivoli Storage Manager ignores this option if you do not specify the fromdate option.

todate[Optional]
	Use the todate option with the totime option to specify an ending date and time to which you want to search for backups or archives during a restore, retrieve, or query operation. For example, you might request a list of files that were backed up before 11:59 PM on June 30, 2002.
	
totime[Optional]
	Use the totime option with the todate option to specify an ending date and time to which you want to search for backups or archives during a restore, retrieve, or query operation. For example, you might request a list of files that were backed up before 11:59 PM on June 30, 2003. Tivoli Storage Manager ignores this option if you do not specify the todate option.

dirsonly[Optional]
	The dirsonly option processes directories only. The client does not process files.

subdir[Optional]
	The subdir option specifies whether you want to include subdirectories of named directories for processing. Valid values-yes,no
Note: SUBDIR is not a valid option when using FILELIST option.

fromnode[Optional]
	The fromnode option permits one node to perform commands for another node. A user on another node must use the set access command to permit you to query, restore, or retrieve files or images for the other node.

ifnewer[Optional]
	The ifnewer option replaces an existing file with the latest backup version only if the backup version is newer than the existing file.

preservepath[Optional]
	The preservepath option specifies how much of the source path to reproduce as part of the target directory path when you restore or retrieve files to a new location. Use the -subdir=yes option to include the entire subtree of the source directory (directories
and files below the lowest-level source directory) as source to be restored. If a required target directory does not exist, it is created. If a target file has the same name as a source file, it is overwritten. Vaild values – 
1) Subtree - Creates the lowest-level source directory as a subdirectory of the target directory. Files from the source directory are stored in the new subdirectory. This is the default.

2) Complete - Restores the entire path, starting from the root, into the specified directory. The entire path includes all the directories except the file space name.

3) NOBase - Restores the contents of the source directory without the lowest level, or base directory, into the specified destination directory.

4) NONe - Restores all selected source files to the target directory. No part of the source path at or above the source directory is reproduced at the target.	

replace[Mandatory]
The replace option specifies whether to overwrite existing files on your workstation, or to prompt you for your selection when you restore or retrieve files.
Valid values are –

All
   All existing files are overwritten, including read-only files. All locked files are replaced when the system is rebooted. If  access to a file is denied, you are prompted to skip or
   overwrite the file. No action is taken on the file until there is a response to the prompt.

Yes
   Existing files are overwritten, except read-only files. For nonscheduled operations, you are asked whether to overwrite existing read-only files. For scheduled operations, existing read-only files are not overwritten and no prompts are displayed. If access to a file is denied, the file is skipped.

No
   Existing files are not overwritten. No prompts will be displayed.

Note: Although user can provide any of the above values however since this adapter does not support prompt handling at the moment, it is advisable to provide either “yes” or “no” here as the value.

skipntpermissions[Optional]
	The skipntpermissions option bypasses processing of NTFS security information. Select this option for incremental backups, selective backups, archives, retrieves and restores. Valid values are –
No
   If you specify No, the NTFS security information is backed up, restored, archived or retrieved. This is the default.

Yes
   If you specify Yes, the NTFS security information is not backed up, restored, archived or retrieved.

skipntsecuritycrc[Optional]
	The skipntsecuritycrc option controls the computation of the security cyclic redundancy check (CRC) for a comparison of NTFS security information during an incremental or selective backup, archive, restore, or retrieve operation. If you set the
skipntsecuritycrc option to no (the default), performance might be slower because the program must retrieve all the security descriptors. Valid values are-
No
   If you specify No, the security CRC is generated during a backup. This is the default.

Yes
   If you specify Yes, the security CRC is not generated during a backup. All the permissions are backed up, but the program will not be able to determine if the permissions are changed during the next incremental backup. When the skipntpermissions option is set to yes, the skipntsecuritycrc option does not apply.

NOTE: Either one of “filespec” or “filelist” should be provided.

followsymbolic[Optional]
	The followsymbolic option specifies whether you want to restore files to symbolic links or use a symbolic link as a virtual mount point.
Valid values:-
No
         Specifies that you do not want to restore to symbolic links, or to use symbolic links as virtual mount points. This is the default.

Yes
         Specifies that you want to restore to symbolic links, or to use a symbolic link as a virtual mount point.
This is valid only for UNIX.
</description>
        <from>items</from>
        <to>items</to>
      </input>
      <output global="false" required="false">
        <to>adapter response</to>
        <from>adapter response</from>
      </output>
    </parameters>
    <access />
    <sequence>
      <call-process>
        <process-name>:AO-AD-IBM_Tivoli_Storage_Manager:Utilities:Execute Request</process-name>
        <parameters>
          <input>
            <from>adapter name</from>
            <to>adapter name</to>
          </input>
          <input>
            <from>items</from>
            <to>items</to>
          </input>
          <input>
            <value>retrieve</value>
            <to>valid operation name</to>
          </input>
          <output>
            <from>adapter response</from>
            <to>adapter response</to>
          </output>
        </parameters>
        <meta>
          <documentation />
          <run-mode-handling>
            <run-mode>OCP</run-mode>
            <allow-step-into>false</allow-step-into>
          </run-mode-handling>
          <checkpoint>false</checkpoint>
        </meta>
        <location>:call-process[1]</location>
      </call-process>
    </sequence>
    <meta>
      <expose-to>
        <consumer>RULE</consumer>
        <consumer>SCHEDULE</consumer>
      </expose-to>
      <documentation>
        <description>This wrapper obtains copies of archived files from the Tivoli Storage Manager server. You can retrieve specific files or entire directories.</description>
        <version></version>
      </documentation>
      <peer-location>
        <location>any</location>
      </peer-location>
      <record-metrics>false</record-metrics>
      <process-id>8744de4c-3fa2-3f03-8b09-8aa58dbedf55</process-id>
      <author />
      <category />
      <status />
      <keywords />
      <systems />
      <last-modified-by />
      <last-modified>1290597031608</last-modified>
    </meta>
  </process-def>
</process>